export const geography =   [
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20country%20is%20not%20a%20part%20of%20Scandinavia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Finland",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Norway",
"Sweden",
"Denmark"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20which%20city%2C%20is%20the%20Big%20Nickel%20located%20in%20Canada%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sudbury%2C%20Ontario",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Calgary%2C%20Alberta",
"Halifax%2C%20Nova%20Scotia%20",
"Victoria%2C%20British%20Columbia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20city%20and%20commercial%20capital%20of%20Sri%20Lanka%3F",
"correct_answer": "Colombo",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Moratuwa",
"Negombo",
"Kandy"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20countries%20is%20NOT%20a%20part%20of%20the%20Asian%20continent%3F",
"correct_answer": "Suriname",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Georgia",
"Russia",
"Singapore"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20island%20countries%20is%20located%20in%20the%20Caribbean%3F",
"correct_answer": "Barbados",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Fiji",
"Maldives",
"Seychelles"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20city%20in%20India%3F",
"correct_answer": "Islamabad",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hyderabad",
"Ahmedabad",
"Ghaziabad"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20prefix%20Sino-%20%28As%20in%20Sino-American%29%20is%20used%20to%20refer%20to%20what%20nationality%3F",
"correct_answer": "Chinese",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Japanese",
"Russian",
"Indian"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20country%20is%20completely%20landlocked%20by%20South%20Africa%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lesotho",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Swaziland",
"Botswana",
"Zimbabwe"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20mountainous%20Khyber%20Pass%20connects%20which%20of%20the%20two%20following%20countries%3F",
"correct_answer": "Afghanistan%20and%20Pakistan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"India%20and%20Nepal",
"Pakistan%20and%20India",
"Tajikistan%20and%20Kyrgyzstan"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20one%20of%20the%20Neo-Aramaic%20languages%20spoken%20by%20the%20Jewish%20population%20from%20Northwestern%20Iraq%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lishana%20Deni",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hulaul%C3%A1",
"Lishan%20Didan",
"Chaldean%20Neo-Aramaic"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%202012%20the%20German-speaking%20microstate%20%22Liechtenstein%22%20in%20Central%20Europe%20had%20a%20population%20of%20how%20many%20inhabitants%3F",
"correct_answer": "36%2C600",
"incorrect_answers": [
"2%2C400",
"90%2C000",
"323%2C400"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Where%20is%20the%20Luxor%20Hotel%20%26%20Casino%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Paradise%2C%20Nevada",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Las%20Vegas%2C%20Nevada",
"Winchester%2C%20Nevada",
"Jackpot%2C%20Nevada"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20year%20is%20on%20the%20flag%20of%20the%20US%20state%20Wisconsin%3F",
"correct_answer": "1848",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1634",
"1783",
"1901"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20countries%20border%20Kyrgyzstan%3F",
"correct_answer": "4",
"incorrect_answers": [
"3",
"1",
"6"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20is%20the%20largest%20freshwater%20lake%20in%20the%20world%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lake%20Superior%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Caspian%20Sea",
"Lake%20Michigan",
"Lake%20Huron"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Where%20is%20the%20fast%20food%20chain%20%22Panda%20Express%22%20headquartered%3F",
"correct_answer": "Rosemead%2C%20California",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sacramento%2C%20California",
"Fresno%2C%20California",
"San%20Diego%2C%20California"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Llanfair%C2%ADpwllgwyngyll%C2%ADgogery%C2%ADchwyrn%C2%ADdrobwll%C2%ADllan%C2%ADtysilio%C2%ADgogo%C2%ADgoch%20is%20located%20on%20which%20Welsh%20island%3F",
"correct_answer": "Anglesey",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Barry",
"Bardsey",
"Caldey"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20area%20of%20Vatican%20City%3F",
"correct_answer": "0.44km%5E2",
"incorrect_answers": [
"0.10km%5E2",
"0.86km%5E2",
"12.00km%5E2"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20Hunua%20Ranges%20is%20located%20in...",
"correct_answer": "New%20Zealand",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nepal",
"China",
"Mexico"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Fucking%20is%20a%20village%20in%20which%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Austria",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Germany",
"Switzerland",
"Czech%20Republic"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20most%20populous%20Muslim-majority%20nation%20in%202010%3F",
"correct_answer": "Indonesia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Saudi%20Arabia",
"Iran",
"Sudan"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20country%20was%20NOT%20formerly%20part%20of%20Yugoslavia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Albania",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Croatia",
"Serbia",
"Macedonia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20official%20German%20name%20of%20the%20Swiss%20Federal%20Railways%3F",
"correct_answer": "Schweizerische%20Bundesbahnen",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Schweizerische%20Nationalbahnen",
"Bundesbahnen%20der%20Schweiz",
"Schweizerische%20Staatsbahnen"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20city%20is%20known%20as%20the%20Rose%20Capital%20of%20the%20World%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tyler%2C%20Texas",
"incorrect_answers": [
"San%20Diego%2C%20California",
"Miami%2C%20Florida",
"Anaheim%2C%20California"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20Finnish%20word%20for%20%22Finland%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Suomi",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Eesti",
"Magyarorsz%C3%A1g",
"Sverige"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20Canadian%20national%20anthem%3F",
"correct_answer": "O%20Canada",
"incorrect_answers": [
"O%20Red%20Maple",
"Leaf-Spangled%20Banner",
"March%20of%20the%20Puck%20Drop"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20North%20American%20tourist%20attraction%20is%20served%20by%20the%20%22Maid%20of%20the%20Mist%22%20tour%20company%3F",
"correct_answer": "Niagara%20Falls",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Whistler%2C%20British%20Columbia",
"Disney%20World",
"Yosemite%20National%20Park"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20rocky%20region%20that%20spans%20most%20of%20eastern%20Canada%3F",
"correct_answer": "Canadian%20Shield",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rocky%20Mountains",
"Appalachian%20Mountains",
"Himalayas"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20tallest%20mountain%20in%20Canada%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mount%20Logan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mont%20Tremblant",
"Whistler%20Mountain",
"Blue%20Mountain"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20Canada%27s%20largest%20island%3F",
"correct_answer": "Baffin%20Island",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Prince%20Edward%20Island",
"Vancouver%20Island",
"Newfoundland"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20formerly%20rich%20fishing%20grounds%20off%20the%20island%20of%20Newfoundland%2C%20Canada%3F",
"correct_answer": "Grand%20Banks",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Great%20Barrier%20Reef",
"Mariana%20Trench",
"Hudson%20Bay"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "When%20does%20Finland%20celebrate%20their%20independence%20day%3F",
"correct_answer": "December%206th",
"incorrect_answers": [
"January%202nd",
"November%2012th",
"February%208th"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20second-largest%20city%20in%20Lithuania%3F",
"correct_answer": "Kaunas",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Panev%C4%97%C5%BEys",
"Vilnius",
"Klaip%C4%97da"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20land%20connecting%20North%20America%20and%20South%20America%3F",
"correct_answer": "Isthmus%20of%20Panama",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Isthmus%20of%20Suez",
"Urals",
"Australasia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20cities%20has%20a%204%C2%B0%20East%20longitude.%20",
"correct_answer": "Amsterdam",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rio%20de%20Janero",
"Toronto",
"Hong%20Kong"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20city%20of%20Bermuda%3F",
"correct_answer": "Hamilton",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Santo%20Dominigo",
"San%20Juan",
"Havana"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "How%20many%20stations%20does%20the%20Central%20Line%20have%20on%20the%20London%20Underground%3F",
"correct_answer": "49",
"incorrect_answers": [
"51",
"43",
"47"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Mauritius%3F",
"correct_answer": "Port%20Louis",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Port%20Moresby",
"Port%20Vila",
"Port-au-Prince"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "In%20which%20country%20is%20Tallinn%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Estonia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Finland",
"Sweden",
"Poland"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20most%20common%20climbing%20route%20for%20the%20second%20highest%20mountain%20in%20the%20world%2C%20K2%3F",
"correct_answer": "Abruzzi%20Spur",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Magic%20Line",
"Cesen%20Route",
"Polish%20Line"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Into%20which%20basin%20does%20the%20Jordan%20River%20flow%20into%3F",
"correct_answer": "Dead%20Sea",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Aral%20Sea",
"Caspian%20Sea",
"Salton%20Sea"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20emblem%20on%20the%20flag%20of%20the%20Republic%20of%20Tajikistan%20features%20a%20sunrise%20over%20mountains%20below%20what%20symbol%3F",
"correct_answer": "Crown",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bird",
"Sickle",
"Tree"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "The%20Maluku%20islands%20%28informally%20known%20as%20the%20Spice%20Islands%29%20belong%20to%20which%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Indonesia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Chile",
"New%20Zealand",
"Fiji"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20national%20museum%20will%20you%20find%20in%20Cooperstown%2C%20New%20York%3F",
"correct_answer": "National%20Baseball%20Hall%20of%20Fame",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Metropolitan%20Museum%20of%20Art",
"National%20Toy%20Hall%20of%20Fame",
"Museum%20of%20Modern%20Art"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20cities%20is%20NOT%20in%20England%3F",
"correct_answer": "Edinburgh",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oxford",
"Manchester",
"Southampton"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20country%20is%20the%20Taedong%20River%20in%3F",
"correct_answer": "North%20Korea",
"incorrect_answers": [
"South%20Korea",
"Japan",
"China"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Wisconsin%2C%20USA%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madison",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Milwaukee",
"Wisconsin%20Dells",
"Green%20Bay"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20a%20real%20tectonic%20plate%3F",
"correct_answer": "Atlantic%20Plate",
"incorrect_answers": [
"North%20American%20Plate",
"Eurasian%20Plate",
"Nazca%20Plate"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Bir%20Tawil%2C%20an%20uninhabited%20track%20of%20land%20claimed%20by%20no%20country%2C%20is%20located%20along%20the%20border%20of%20which%20two%20countries%3F",
"correct_answer": "Egypt%20and%20Sudan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Israel%20and%20Jordan",
"Chad%20and%20Libya",
"Iraq%20and%20Saudi%20Arabia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "hard",
"question": "Which%20is%20not%20a%20country%20in%20Africa%3F",
"correct_answer": "Guyana",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Senegal",
"Liberia",
"Somalia"
]
}
]